[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Todd Akin"]}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What do you think is going on here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, the Republicans are just in a dither over what Todd Akin said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Republican Platform Committee"]}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RBS", ":", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "And if you're looking at this from the outside, you're saying, well, what do these guys really believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, and we'll find out some more tomorrow because the Republican Platform Committee is going to have a vote on whether or not the human life amendment, which would ban most -- almost all abortions, I believe only maybe the life of the mother would be an exception.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Margaret, this is a real mess, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes, we could have asked for a better story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "I mean if they believe that, why don't they just say it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, you know, perhaps they will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Yes, he's not Mitt Romney, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I mean --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 127, "question": "So how can he -- how can he use this issue to drive people out of office?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, Piers --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "So, again where is his credibility on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, what is interesting is that the platform committee votes for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "This is the very last thing that Mitt Romney wanted to blow up, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, certainly Republicans don't like talking about social issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Why isn't he gone yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, nobody can make him go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Have you any idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Well, I don't know about the semantics of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "What do you have to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "ILVER: I think the problem is that people's imagination might almost be worse with all the different possibilities of what it could be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Ben, very quickly on the tax, do you think he should release more?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I mean I think yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What is your reaction to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, my reaction is to not talk publicly about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Do you find it odd that we're still even debating this in 2012?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "It's disappointing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2012"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week"]}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What kind of thing are you going to be really getting into from a personal point of view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "For example, last week, we did a show on hormones.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "How you feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I'm not nervous from the standpoint I have done it before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Did you ever meet her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "You know, I have a feeling I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "What is the secret to getting over the low parts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "I think for me, it's being true to myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "How have things moved on since then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "It's pretty much stayed the same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "This is what your kind of viewers are going through on a daily basis, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Can I help you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "You have already?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Does she know really what brought this on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "WP", "RB", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "How many Twitter followers do you have now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Only 165,000.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "How about you, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I'm glad you asked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ":", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "But when people are really nasty or vicious, how do you deal with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I don't really see -- people, thank goodness, have been really nice to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Can you do anything about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What's your address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Ricki lake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy Savio"]}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Why are you so convinced of your client's innocence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Well, there's absolutely no evidence, and I mean no evidence that he was anywhere near Kathy Savio's house that date that she died.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "It was a pretty strange set of facts if it doesn't involve homicide, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Well, not really when you look at it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rob Lowe", "Jim Glasgow"]}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "If so, what did you think of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "First, I thought that Rob Lowe looked more like the state's attorney, Jim Glasgow, than he did like Drew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", ":", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Does it matter in a criminal case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "The only -- to some extent it does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stacey Peterson"]}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Do you have any theories yourself about what happened to Stacey Peterson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I mean, Stacey Peterson is an ongoing investigation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stacey Peterson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "What kind of guy is he when there are no cameras around and he's not showing off a bit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "He's actually a very down to Earth guy, a very personable guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "What are they going to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "I know who's not going to be a member.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Who, me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "You.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]